Finding aid for Bentley Historical Library records, 1919 - 2014
Bentley Historical Library
- Division Records
  - University Archives and Records Program (UARP), 1973-2004
    - MeMail Project
      - Unstructured Data Repositories at University of Michigan, 2009 (Box 69)
    - Staff Files
      - Affirmative Action Discovery, 1998 (Box 76)
      - Cloud Computing, 2010-2011; 2 folders (Box 76)
      - Marilyn McNitt, Associate Archivist
        - Exhibits
          - Gargoyle Exhibit, 1999; 2 folders (Box 76)
          - Solar Car Exhibit, undated (Box 76)
          - General, 1991-1994; 2013 (Box 76)
        - UARP Discussion on Processing, 2005 (Box 76)
        - Reports-Monthly/Quarterly, 1985-1987 (Box 76)
        - University of Michigan-Dearborn Records Project, 1992-2000 (Box 76)
      - Nancy Deromedi, Associate Archivist
        - Architecture, 2011-2013 (Box 76)
          (includes photos)
        - Blogs, 2005-2009 (Box 76)
        - Brown vs. Board Website, 1999-2005 (Box 76)
        - Computing, 2003-2011 (Box 76)
        - Copenhagen, Denmark, 2009 (Box 76)
        - Duderstadt, James, 1989-2007; 2 folders (Box 76)
        - Interim Repository, 2010-2011 (Box 76)
        - Mblog, 2006-2013 (Box 76)
        - Mellon Grant-"Case Studies and the Effective Management of University Digital Records", 2006-2008 (Box 76)
        - Miscellaneous, 1998-2012 (Box 76)
        - National Historical Publications and Records Commission (NHPRC) Faculty Websites Research Grant, 2002-2006 (Box 76)
        - Presentations, 1998-2003; 2 folders (Box 77)
        - President's Office Website, 2004-2005 (Box 77)
        - Reports
          - "An Analysis of the University of Michigan's Electronic Front Door", 2000 (Box 77)
          - General, 2011-2013 (Box 77)
        - Retreat, 2011 (Box 77)
        - SAA Electronic Records Section (ERS) Program Proposals, 2000-2004 (Box 77)
      - Tracking, 2001-2003 (Box 77)
- Outreach: Education, Publicity, and Exhibits
  The Outreach subgroup (1929-2014, 10 linear feet, 149 MG) documents various forms of public outreach and is divided into three series: Archival Education, Press Clippings, and Exhibits.
  - Archival Education
    The Archival Education series (1971-2012, 1.1 linear feet) contains lecture notes, syllabi, and planning correspondence for archives course taught by Bentley staff members. Courses include the Library Science 727, School of Information and Library Studies (SILS) 600, 637, and 692, School of Information (SI) 692 Archives Practicum, and History 698 and include lecture notes from Nancy Bartlett, Marilyn McLaughlin and Mary Jo Pugh. Course topics include Problems in Archival Administration and Archival Appraisal. There are two overlapping accessions of files in this series, one containing materials dated 1971-2002 and the second 1977-2012.
    - 1971-1977 (Box 42)
    - SILS 600 (Administration of Archives), 1979-1990 (Box 42)
    - Lectures, Nancy Bartlett (Box 42)
    - Lectures, Mary Jo Pugh (Box 42)
    - SILS 637 (Problems in Archives Administration), 1990-1991 (Box 42)
    - SILS 692 (Archival Practicum), 1990 (Box 42)
    - SILS 727/728 (Problems in Archival Administration; Administration of Archives) (Box 42)
    - Dissertation Committee, 1986-1989; undated (Box 42)
    - SI 692 Archives Practicum, 1998 (Box 42)
    - SI 692 Appraisal Module Archives Practicum, 1999-2002; 3 folders (Box 42)
    - Administration of Archives Class: Library Science 727, 1979 (Box 70)
    - Archives class development, 1993-1994 (Box 70)
    - Archives Program Rosters, 1977-1981 (Box 70)
    - History 698: Processing the past: Experience, authority and the institutions of social memory, 2003 (Box 70)
    - Lectures for audio session, Marilyn McLaughlin, 1993 (Box 70)
    - Library Science 727: Administration of Archives, 1979 (Box 70)
    - Rackham 570, SI 637, History 796: Documenting the slave experience, 2002 (Box 70)
    - SI 692: Archival practicum, 1982-2012
      - General, 2005-2007 (Box 70)
      - Collection development module, 2006-2012 (Box 70)
      - Planning, 1996-2000 (Box 70)
      - Rosters, 1982-2003 (Box 70)
      - Syllabi, 1982-2003 (Box 70)
  - Clippings (newspaper and press)
    The Press Clippings series (1935-1986, 0.3 linear feet), contains 20 folders of newspapers and magazine clipping that feature the Michigan Historical Collection, the Bentley Library, or a use of one of their collections. These clippings help document the early years of the MCH with publicity for Director Vander Velde and notes on various collections donated to MHC. Later folders contain official press releases from the university on prominent donations and grant awards.
    - Clippings, 1938-1986; 20 folders (Box 42)
  - Exhibits
    The Exhibits series (1929-2014, 7.5 linear feet, one oversize box, 149 MG) is comprised of material prepared by BHL staff for both internal and external exhibits. Most of the files contain the corresponding display labels; for some there are also photocopies of source material and background information. The series is arranged alphabetically by the title of the exhibit and consists of two accessions dated 1929-2007 (7 linear feet) and 1998-2013 (0.5 linear feet). A chronological listings of exhibits, 1929-1961, and newspaper clippings regarding exhibits, 1943-1959, precede the individual exhibit files. There are five boxes of Exhibit material (images and labels on poster board) from an exhibit on Michigan in the Olympics, on Women at the University of Michigan from 1870 to the Present, and from miscellaneous images from the Bentley Library.
    Researchers should note that several exhibits are individually cataloged. The latter includes University of Michigan Sesquicentennial Celebration Exhibition photograph collection, A Gallery of presidents, Goin' north: Black Detroit and the great migration, 1910-1930, and Centennial of the admission of Women to the University of Michigan exhibition. An additional group of online materials and special projects includes exhibit materials created or displayed on the BHL's website from 2001 to 2014.
    - Chronological Listing of Exhibits, 1929-1961 (Box 43)
    - Newspaper Clippings (re: exhibits), 1943-1959 (Box 43)
    - Academies and Colleges, 1952 (Box 43)
    - American Frontier in an Ann Arbor Attic, 1969 (Box 43)
    - American-Philippines Relations, 1983 (Box 43)
    - Angell, James B. and Smith, Shirley W., 1955 (Box 43)
    - Angell, James B., 1971 (Box 43)
    - Angell, James Burrill, 1945 (Box 43)
    - Ann Arbor, 1939; 1944; 1946 (Box 43)
    - Ann Arbor in the Centennial Period, 1977 (Box 43)
    - Ann Arbor Christmas, 1930; 1992 (Box 43)
    - Art of Football 1894-1994 100 Years of Football Programs, Posters, and Ephemera, 1995, 1894-1995 (Box 43)
    - Autographs, 1948 (Box 43)
    - Bachman, Werner E., 1983 (Box 43)
    - Bentley, Alvin, 1969 (Box 43)
    - Bentley, Alvin, 1983 (Box 43)
    - Brown, Prentiss, 1977 (Box 43)
    - Business Records, 1954 (Box 43)
    - Campus, 1941; 1942; 1952 (Box 43)
    - Centennial of the Admission of Women, 1970 (Box 43)
      (copy prints separately cataloged as Centennial of the admission of women to the University of Michigan photograph collection)
    - China and University of Michigan, 1979 (Box 43)
    - Chinese Exhibit, 2001 (Box 43)
    - Christmas, undated (Box 43)
    - Churches, 1951 (Box 43)
    - Civil War Envelopes, 1976 (Box 43)
    - Cold Noses, Warm Hearts: Dogs in Michigan, 1993 (Box 43)
    - Commencement, 1950 (Box 43)
    - Conservation of Earliest Documents of University of Michigan, 1983 (Box 43)
    - Cooley, Thomas Mortimer, 1942 (Box 43)
    - Cost of Living, 1951-1952 (Box 43)
    - D-Day Plus 40, 1994 (Box 43)
    - Detroit Transportation, 2001 (Box 43)
    - Diaries, 1942; 1952 (Box 43)
    - Discovering and Exploring Women's Sources at the Bentley and Clements Libraries, 2002 (Box 43)
    - Douglas, Lloyd Cassel, Minister and Novelist, 1960 (Box 43)
    - Dutch in Michigan, 1947-1948 (Box 43)
    - Dutch in Michigan, 1986 (Box 43)
    - Economics Building, 1982 (Box 43)
    - Education, 1945 (Box 43)
    - Environmental Movement in Michigan, 1988 (Box 43)
    - Everyday Archives: Public Uses of Images from the Bentley, 2006 (Box 43)
    - Faces of Ellis Is, 1986 (Box 43)
    - Felch, Alpheus, (undated) (Box 43)
    - Ford, Gerald, 1979 (Box 43)
    - Francis, Thomas, 1993-1994 (Box 43)
    - Freshmen, 1946 (Box 43)
    - Germans in Michigan, 1983-1984 (Box 43)
    - Goin' north: Black Detroit and the great migration (copy prints separately cataloged as Going north: Black Detroit and the great migration, 1910-1930), 1991 (Box 43)
    - Good Roads Movement (Box 43)
    - Hall, Emma, 1980 (Box 43)
    - Hayden, Joseph Ralston, 1955-1956 (Box 43)
    - History at Michigan, 100 Years, 1958 (Box 43)
    - Houghton, Douglass, 1945 (Box 43)
    - Houghton, Douglass, 1982 (Box 43)
    - Huron River, 1998 (Box 43)
    - Information Technology at ISR, 1998 (Box 43)
    - Jensen, Jens (Friends Meeting), 1997 (Box 43)
    - John Harvey Kellogg: The Battle Creek Idea, 1994-1995 (Box 43)
    - Joy, Henry B., 1996 (Box 43)
    - Kalamazoo, 1955 (Box 43)
    - Kick Out the Jams! The MC5 Rocks Detroit, 2001 (Box 43)
    - Lamination, 1974 (Box 43)
    - Letters from the White House, 1978 (Box 44)
    - Local Color: Dan Bradt's Watercolors from Michigan Historic Scenes, 2002 (Box 44)
    - Lumbering, 1951 (Box 44)
    - Magic and the Supernatural in Michigan, 1993-1994 (Box 44)
    - Maps and Prints from the Earl De La Vergne Collection, 1984-1985 (Box 44)
    - Mason, Stevens T., 1961 (Box 44)
    - May Festival, 1949 (Box 44)
    - Medical Photography at the University of Michigan, 1995 (Box 44)
    - Medical School, 1947; 1950; 1953; 1956 (Box 44)
    - Men of Conscience, 1990 (Box 44)
    - Men in Tights (and dresses and lipstick and rouge) 100 Years of the Michigan Union Opera, 2008 (Box 44)
    - Michigan and the Movies, 1982 (Box 44)
    - Michigan and the Presidency, 1992-1993 (Box 44)
    - Michigan Historical Collections, 1948 (Box 44)
    - Michigan Historical Collections (some copy prints in oversized box 40), 1969 (Box 44)
    - Michigan Historical Commission, 1952 (Box 44)
    - Michigan Imprints (Box 44)
    - Michigan in Four Centuries, 1954 (Box 44)
    - Michigan Indians, 1979 (Box 44)
    - Michigan on the, March, 1995; 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Michigan Media, 1990 (Box 44)
    - Michigan Men in Presidential Campaigns, 1948 (Box 44)
    - Michigan Men in the Civil War, 1959; 1961 (Box 44)
    - Michigan Politics in the, 1950s; 1985 (Box 44)
    - Michigan Prior to, 1850; 1948 (Box 44)
    - Michigan Promise and Performance, 1985; 1987 (Box 44)
    - Michigan Takes Shape (Maps), 1946-1947 (Box 44)
    - Michigan Union Opera, 1949 (Box 44)
    - Michigan's 298th General Hospital, 1993 (Box 44)
    - Michigan in the Olympics, 1992 (Box 44)
      (see also Crisler Arena exhibit material in Boxes 47-49)
    - Mining, 1952 (Box 44)
    - Monroe, Michigan, 1950 (Box 44)
    - Monteith Library, 1976 (Box 44)
    - Moody, Blair, 1957 (Box 44)
    - National Housewives League, 2000 (Box 44)
    - Native Peoples in Transition, 1989 (Box 44)
      (copy prints separately cataloged as Native peoples in transition: Michigan Indians in the nineteenth century)
    - Newspapers, 1951 (Box 44)
    - Northern Peninsula, 1955 (Box 44)
    - One Hundred and Fifty Years of Student Life, 1987 (Box 44)
    - One Hundred Thirty Years of Political Campaigning in Michigan, 1958 (Box 44)
    - One Hundred Years of the Michigan Experience in China, 1986; 1999 (Box 44)
    - Osborn Dedication, 1976 (Box 44)
    - Piety and Paideia on the Frontier: The Library of Gabriel Richard, 1985 (Box 44)
    - Poetry Here and Now, 1997 (Box 45)
    - Political Campaigns (Box 45)
    - Pond, Irving Kane, 1949 (Box 45)
    - Pontiac, Michigan, 1938 (Box 45)
    - Printing before, 1851; 1945 (Box 45)
    - Randolph Rogers Exhibit, 1948 (Box 45)
    - Red Mitten: Michigan's Radical Left1900-1960, 2007 (Box 45)
    - Representative Items of the Michigan Historical Collections, 1947 (Box 45)
    - Researching Ann Arbor's Yesterdays, 1985 (Box 45)
    - Schools, 1946; 1950; 1955 (Box 45)
    - Sesquicentennial Exhibit, 1967 (Box 45)
      (copy prints separately cataloged as University of Michigan Sesquicentennial Celebration Exhibition photograph collection)
    - Shakespeare on Campus, 2000-2001 (Box 45)
    - Shaw, Wilfred Byron, 1950 (Box 45)
    - Smith, Charles Spencer, 1983 (Box 45)
    - Smith, Gerald L. K., 1984 (Box 45)
    - A Sporting Chance: Women's Athletics at the University of Michigan, 2000 (Box 45)
    - State and Local History Organizations, 1947 (Box 45)
    - Student Scrapbook: The Michigan Experience, 2007 (Box 45)
    - Stoner Exhibition, 1981 (Box 45)
    - Student Letters of WWII, 1945 (Box 45)
    - Student Life and Customs, 1953 (Box 45)
    - Student Publications, 1941; 1949; 1957 (Box 45)
    - Swedes in Michigan, 1984 (Box 45)
    - Tappan, Henry Phillip, 1942; 1943; 1953 (Box 45)
    - There's Gold in the Collections: Personal Narratives from the California Gold Rush, 2000 (Box 45)
    - Tourists in Michigan, 1949; 1950 (Box 45)
    - The University in the Civil War, 1942-1943 (Box 45)
    - University Development (after 1955) (Box 45)
    - University in the World War I, 1943 (Box 45)
    - University of Michigan, 1944 (Box 45)
    - University of Michigan in, 1904; 1954 (Box 45)
    - University of Michigan in Detroit, 1951 (Box 45)
    - University of Michigan at the First Rose Bowl-1902, 1976-1977 (Box 45)
    - University of Michigan Law School, 1959 (Box 45)
    - University Presidents, 1980; 3 folders (Box 45)
      (copy prints separately cataloged as University President's Exhibition photograph collection)
    - University Snow Scenes (Box 45)
    - University Student Work, 1952-1976 (Box 45)
    - Valentines, 1976; 1981 (Box 45)
    - Valentines, 1985 (Box 45)
    - Vandenberg Exhibition, 1974 (Box 45)
    - Williams Room Dedication, 1975 (Box 45)
    - Williams, G. Mennen, 1970 (Box 45)
    - Women at the University of Michigan from 1870 to the Present, (see box 36 for the plates), 2000-2001 (Box 45)
    - Women's Athletics at University of Michigan, 1979-1980 (Box 45)
    - Women's Suffrage: A Natural Right, 1995 (Box 45)
    - Yost, Fielding Harris, 1949 (Box 45)
    - Women at the University of Michigan from 1870 to the Present, 2001-2002 (Box 46)
      (copy prints on foam mounting used in exhibit at Lane Hall)
    - Michigan in the Olympics, exhibit mounted at University of Michigan Crisler Arena, circa 2003-2005 (Box 47)
    - Michigan in the Olympics, exhibit mounted at University of Michigan Crisler Arena, circa 2003-2005 (Box 48)
    - Michigan in the Olympics, exhibit mounted at University of Michigan Crisler Arena, circa 2003-2005 (Box 49)
    - Student Life Exhibit, copy prints (from Student Activities Building) (Box 49)
    - Miscellaneous exhibit copy prints (Box 50)
      (includes Michigan Historical Collections, material and photographs from the exhibit: From Scholarly Promise to Achievement, 1969)
    - A Cosmopolitan Tradition: International Students at the University Since, 1847; 2007 (Box 70)
    - Documenting Michigan: 20 Collections from the Bentley Historical Library, 2013 (Box 70)
    - The Gargoyle Trawls the Depths of Humor: 100 Years of Cartoons and Quips at the University of Michigan, 2009; 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Imperialism and Reform: The First and Second Philippine Commissions, 1998 (Box 70)
    - Mary Sue Coleman, 2014 (Box 70)
    - Michigan in 3D, 2012; 2 folders (Box 70)
    - Michigan Modernism: Architecture and Archives at the University of Michigan, undated (Folder 1)
      (poster)
    - Primary sources, undated (Box 70)
    - Queer Timeline, 2012 (Box 77)
    - Queer Timeline, 2012 (Folder 1)
    - Rally Round the Flag (Civil War), 2011 (Box 70)
    - Seventy Fifth Anniversary Exhibit, 2010 (Box 70)
    - Star gazing: 150 years of Astronomy at the University, 2009 (Box 70)
    - Symphony Band Exhibit, 2011 (Box 70)
    - University of Michigan Student work, 1852-1976; undated (Box 70)
    - Varsity Vogue: Women's Fashions at the University of Michigan, 2010 (Box 70)
    - Online Materials and Special Projects
      - 75 Years of-at the Bentley Historical Library, 2010; .PDF files
      - A Book of Days: 150 Years of Student Life, 2007; .PDF files
      - A Century of Vacationing and Travel in Michigan, 2010; .PDF files
      - A Cosmopolitan Tradition: International Student, 2007; .PDF files
      - A Decade of Dissent Student Protests at the University of Michigan, 2006; .PDF files
      - A Historical Tour of the University of Michigan Campus, 2007; .PDF files
      - A Queer Timeline, 2012; .PDF files
      - Bentley Historical Library Construction, 2004-2005; .ZIP file
      - Bright Sheng Collection, 2005, .PDF files
      - Caps, Canes, Pushball and Smokers: Student Life at the University of Michigan in the late 1800s and early 1900s, 2013; .PDF files
      - The Great Society Speech: President Lyndon Johnson's 1964 University of Michigan Commencement Speech, 2013; .PDF files
      - The Huron River, 2007; .PDF files
      - John Sinclair, 2007; .PDF files
      - Law School Records at the University of Michigan, 2001; .PDF files
      - The Making of University of Michigan History: The People, Events, and Buildings that Shaped the University, 2007; .PDF files
      - Michigan Daily Alumni Photographers Project, 2005; 2014; .ZIP files
      - Michigan in 3-D, 2012; .ZIP file
      - Rally Round the Flag! Commerating the Civil War, 2011; .PDF files
      - Regents of the University of Michigan, 2012; .PDF files
      - The Seals of the University of Michigan, 2013; .PDF files
      - Stargazing: 150 Years of Astronomy at the University of Michigan, 2009; .PDF files
      - Student Scrapbooks: The Michigan Experience, 2007; .PDF files
      - Tappan's Vision, 2011; .PDF files
      - University of Michigan Timelines, 2002; .PDF files
      - Women of Michigan, 2007; .PDF files
  - Digital Curation
    The Digital Curation series, 2011-2013, includes papers written by unit staff as well as documentation of strategies and procedures employed by the unit for the processing, description, and preservation of born-digital and digitized archives. Access to these materials is provided digitally through active hyperlinks.
    - Papers
      - "Digital Reformatting Procedures" (Matt Adair), 2011; .PDF file
      - "Removable Media and the Use of Digital Forensics" (Miriely Guerrero), 2012; .PDF file
      - "Automating Digital Processing at the Bentley Historical Library" (Michael Shallcross and Nancy Deromedi), 2012; .PDF file
    - Strategies and Procedures
      - AutoPro (Automated Digital Processing Tool) User Manual, 2012-2013; .PDF file
      - Bentley Historical Library Digital Processing Note, 2012-2013; .PDF file
      - Digital Processing Workflow, 2011-2013; .PDF file
      - Format Conversion Guidelines for Long-Term Preservation, 2011; .PDF file
      - Guidelines for the Description of Digital Materials in Finding Aids, 2012-2013; .PDF file
      - Guidelines for the Manual Processing of Born-Digital Materials, 2011; .PDF file
      - Web Archiving Policies
        - Collection Development, 2011; .PDF file
        - Methodology for the Acquisition of Content, 2011; .PDF file
        - Quality Assurance Guidelines, 2011; .PDF file
- Audio-Visual Material
  The Audio-Visual Material series (1967-2011, circa 6 linear feet) contains five subseries: Bentley Publication Production Files, Works of Art: Inventory and Object Files, Photographs, Audiotapes and Videotapes, DVDs, Digital Media and Films.
  - Bentley Publication Production Files
    The Bentley Publication Production Files series (1988-2007, 1 linear foot) consists of early drafts and electronic final drafts of a number of Bentley Library publications including Bentley Bulletins. One particularly well-documented publication is The Book of Days which was both a publication and an exhibit. There is a separate finding aid for the Bentley's publications, which should be consulted for the complete run of printed materials
    - Bentley Library Annual Report, 2004-2005 (Box 51)
    - Bentley Library Annual Report, 2004-2005 (Box 51)
    - Bentley Library History
      - The Bentley Historical Library: Its History and Purpose, October 2004
      - Posner Prize Documents, 2002-2004
      - Map of the Territories of Michigan and Ouisconsin Photograph Identifications, undated
    - Book of Days
      (see also photographs in Box 10)
      - Exhibit, 1988 (Box 51)
      - Readings at Exhibit Opening, 1988 (Box 51)
      - Hamer/Kegan Award, 1988 (Box 51)
      - Notes and Correspondence (Box 51)
      - Photographic Prints and Labels Not Used (Box 51)
      - Photocopies (Box 51)
      - Publicity, 1988 (Box 51)
    - Century of Connectivity at the University of Michigan publication, 2007 (Box 51)
    - Not Perfect, But Just Right: Craven Captions, Forward, Tour and pictures
      (Includes a publication and its forward and captions. The publication was written by James W. Craven about the conservation lab at the Bentley Historical Library.)
      - Bulletin and Documents, 2003
      - Photographs, 2003
    - Presidential Library Comes to Ann Arbor, 2007 (Box 51)
      - Scanned Images
        (Includes some of the scans found in the published work.)
    - UM and China, 1845-2006 (Box 51)
    - [See box 53 for publication photographs] (Box 51)
  - Works of Art: Inventory and Object Files
    The Works of Art: Inventory and Object Files, 1962-2014, bulk 1975-1987 (1 linear foot) are a set of inventory files describing Bentley art objects. Documentation includes Painting Report Forms, catalogue sheet, notes on the piece of artwork and its acquisition, appraisal, artist biography notes and articles, some photographs of the artwork, and some correspondence about the art work. These files were initially created by archivist May Davis Hill and were not maintained after her departure. One file from 2014 details the framed artwork displayed at the Bentley as of that date.
    - Bicentennial Inventory of American Paintings Executive before 1914 National Collection of Fine Arts, 1976 (Box 52)
    - Guide to the Works of Art in Public Areas, Bentley Library, January 1976 (Box 52)
    - Inventory of Framed Art at the Bentley, 2011-2014 (Box 52)
    - Object Files
      - African Mask (Egung Mask) 19-20th Century (Box 52)
      - African Torso (female) 19th Century (Box 52)
      - American, Unknown Artist
        - Portrait of Dr. Ephraim Adams, 19th Century (Box 52)
        - Portrait of John Allen (1796-1851) (Box 52)
        - Portrait of Abel Bingham, 19th Century (Box 52)
        - Portrait of Henry Crapo, 19th Century (Box 52)
        - Governors of Michigan, 1805-1873 (Box 52)
        - Jackson Wagon Sunflower Band, 19th Century (Box 52)
        - John Monteith and Family, ambrotype (Box 52)
        - Medical Building, University of Michigan (photograph), 19th century (Box 52)
        - Portrait of Steven T. Mason (Box 52)
        - Portrait of Polly Palmer Root, 19th Century (Box 52)
        - Portrait of Erastus Root, 19th Century (Box 52)
        - Portrait of James Fairbairn Smith (negatives) (Box 52)
        - View of New Baltimore, 19th Century (Box 52)
    - Decorative Arts
      - Bandolier (Native American), 19th Century (Box 52)
      - Bonisteel--Sofa and Chairs, 19th Century (Box 52)
      - Ch'ing Pai Bowl, Sung Dynasty (960-1280 A.D.) (Box 52)
      - Dutch, Tiles (tulip design), 18-19th Century (Box 52)
      - Kendi Spouted Vase, 19th Century (Box 52)
      - Ladle, Tiffany & Co., 20th Century (Box 52)
      - Rugs (general), 2 folders (Box 52)
      - Rug (Persian), 19th Century (Box 52)
      - Rug (Yazd), 20th Century (Box 52)